<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Karatbars VBC</string>
    <string name="nav_news">News</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faqs">FAQs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_karatbars">Karatbars</string>
    <string name="title_activity_news">News</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bienvenidos">Welcome</string>
    <string name="main_card0_title_0">Welcome</string>
    <string name="main_card0_title_1">Presentation of Karatbars</string>
    <string name="main_card0_title_2">More details</string>
    <string name="main_card0_title_3">Here</string>
    <string name="boton_karatbars_video_1">Watch Video 1</string>
    <string name="boton_karatbars_video_2">Watch Video 2</string>
    <string name="boton_karatbars_video_3">Watch Video 3</string>
    <string name="boton_karatbars_registrarse">CLICKING HERE</string>
    <string name="donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="text_karatbars_1">\n\nYou may be looking for a solid way to prosper in your life.\n\nRegardless of your current personal, economic or work situation, here you will discover that the business option offered by Karatbars International is among the brightest in the world, and that you can start it in parallel to your current activity.\nKaratbars International has physical offices in:\n\n1- Stuttgart\n2- Thailand\n3- Czech Republic\n4- New York\n5- Slovenia\n6- Spain\n7- Colombia\n8- Costa Rica\n\nIt has a range of highly exclusive products, which are delivered to customers\' homes through FedEx and Prosegur, these two world-renowned companies are associated with Karatbars International.\n\nIt is a business based on a product that everyone knows, gold, and simple because it is easily duplicable.\n\nThe vision of Karatbars International is innovative, and the concept, very powerful: already established in more than 120 countries, our main objective is to make it possible for everyone to have gold, regardless of their purchasing power. From only 1 gram and also be able to do it on a monthly basis in the smartest savings plan of the entire market.\n\nKaratbars has understood the security that physical investment gold provides to anyone to protect their money from inflation and currency devaluation. The \"paper currency\" loses value daily. Gold is limited and will reach an unthinkable value when reserves are exhausted.\n\nChoose a quiet place, disconnect for a moment from the world and take your time.\n\nStart with the first video and quietly follow until the last.\n\nI\'m sure you\'ll love it ...\n</string>
    <string name="text_karatbars_2">\nHow do I start in the business?\n\n1- Register as an affiliate for free</string>
    <string name="text_karatbars_3">\n2-Send your KYC documents (identity document and domiciliary receipt (they are necessary to avoid money laundering) these documents take up to 1 day to be approved.  \n\n3-Acquire your license by purchasing a BUSINESS PACK (SILVER, GOLD, VIP OR VIP EXCLUSIVE).  \n\n4-Once you have completed the previous steps your sponsor will contact you to create a work plan and provide all the necessary work tools and information.</string>
    <string name="text_karatbars_4">\nWhat does the Karatbars International franchise offer you?\n\nCreate your own business and work with the best and most prestigious gold sales company in Germany, recognized by the BDS (the most important federation of savers in the country) as the best and most reliable option to invest in gold in small bullion from only 1 gram.\n\nYou will have a product that is a natural resource appreciated throughout the world. Pure gold, 24 carat 999.9 thousandths of purity and with the best certifications that exist, including the LBMA certificate.\n</string>
    <string name="text_karatbars_5">\nWe will show you the most frequent reasons why people decide to join.\n\nExtra Income\nFinancial Freedom\nHaving a business\nHave time\nPersonal development\nHelp others\nMeet new people\nBetter Retirement\nLeave Inheritance\n\nBefore getting into the question, we must remember:\n\nSUCCESS or FAILURE DEPENDS 100% ON YOU.\nACCEPT THE RESPONSIBILITY OF EVERYTHING YOU HAVE.\nIT DECIDES TO BE PROFESSIONAL.\nAccept RESPONSIBILITY.\n\nNow ask yourself these three questions:\n\nDo I want to overcome the current moment in which I am?\nDo I have an hour a day?\nCan I commit myself?\n\nIf your answers are affirmative, it is time to act ...\n</string>
    <string name="text_karatbars_6">\nGold - Karatbars International\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="main_card1_button">Follow Reading...</string>
    <string name="main_card1_subtitle">You may be looking for a solid way to thrive in your life...</string>
    <string name="main_card1_title">Karatbars International GmbH</string>
    <string name="main_card2_button">Details...</string>
    <string name="about_email_intent">About:KaratbarsVBC</string>
    <string name="main_card2_title2">Cryptocurrencies Karatbars</string>
    <string name="large_text_buy_kbc">\nBuy KBC in the best EXCHANGE\n\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_1">\n\nKaratGold Coin (KBC)</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_2">\nKaratGold Coin (KBC) is a cryptocurrency based on blockchain. Specifically designed to be used as a means of electronic payment generally accepted for all who consider gold as a traditional, true, safe and stable value means.</string>
    <string name="button_cripto_video_presentacion">Watch Video Presentation</string>
    <string name="button_cripto_video_entrevista">Interview Harald Seiz</string>
    <string name="dialog_close">Close</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_3">\nProblem\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_4">In other times, gold was a means of direct payment, especially in the form of gold coins. However, gold has been continuously replaced by bank notes, which currently do not have, or only have a marginal percentage, the support of state gold. Therefore, the value of the bills issued by the different countries is based on the confidence that the respective country can pay their bills. Only this is less secure than in other times. Especially in less developed countries, the reliability of legal tender moves towards zero.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_5">Solution</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_6">\nKaratGold Coin responds perfectly to global needs because it is based on gold. Each coin represents a certain weight of gold and can at all times be exchanged in physical gold in the form of CashGold. In addition, it can be exchanged for all fiduciary and cryptocurrency currencies around the world.\n\nThe currency is crypted gold that can be transferred without borders, in a profitable, safe and real time manner. Its value is predictable because the value of gold has a long tradition and everyone has an idea about its stability. Therefore, the Currency has the ability to be generally accepted throughout the world.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_7">\nDetails about the currency:\n\nThe \"Currency\" is based on the Ethereum blockchain protocol. Therefore, it is safe, profitable and fast. In addition, it allows you to use smart contracts within your protocol.\n\nToken name:\tKaratGold Coin\nTicker Symbol:\tKBC\nStarting Price: Pre-ICO 1 KBC for USD 0.01\nStarting Price: ICO 1 KBC for USD 0.05\nMaximum KBC produced:\t12 billion (technical limit)\nMaximum KBC for Sale:\t7.2 billion\nFundraising Goal:\tUSD 72 million\nMethods of KBC purchase:\tBitcoin, Ethereum, Dash, Litecoin, XEM and FIAT payments\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_8">\n\nKaratCoinBank (KCB)</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_9">\nThe Currency of the first Cryptobank of the world.\nCovered by an innovative and recently developed blockchain technology, KaratCoinBank (KCB) is a transparent cryptocurrency, with Blockchain, we can all see where and how gold is stored and which speculative currency is covered with gold.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_cripto_10">\nDetails about the currency:\n\nName of Token: KaratCoin Bank Coin\nTicker symbol: KCB\nStandard Token: ERC20\nThe current price: 0.14 €\nMaximum amount of KCB for sale: 50 billion\nFundraising goal: 1 billion\nMinimum purchase: 1000 KCB\nPayment methods: BTC, ETH y KaratPAY\n</string>
    <string name="share_with">Share with...</string>
    <string name="app_designed_by">Designed by YoelRP in Cuba</string>
    <string name="activity_my_apps">Karatbars Apps</string>
    <string name="title_activity_crypto">Cryptocurrencies</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_1">\n\nWho is Karatbars International?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_2">www.karatbars.com is the homepage of the Karatbars group. This company is designed to sell precious metals, especially small gold ingots, embedded in design cards that include certifications. Thanks to our independent activity of banks, we can offer a selection of suitable products without the influence of external social interests.\n\nKaratbars International is a commercial company present on the Internet and its products can be sent all over the world, to a list of increasingly larger and constantly expanding countries.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_3">\nIs Karatbars legal?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_4">Yes, Karatbars is a company legally registered in Germany and complies with the current legislation of the more than 120 countries in which it has opened its operations.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_5">\nWhat product does Karatbars International offer?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_6">The Karatbars group offers the most extraordinary range of products on the market. Karatbars gold bars have the highest quality standards.\n\nAtasay \"(in Turkey) is the producer and supplier of our one-gram gold bars of the\" ATAKULCHE \"brand. This company has been included in the London Bullion Market Association (LBMA), with the seal \"Good Delivery\" since 07/05/2010, which guarantees the stability of production and supplies. In this refinery, we have our own production chain, so we can be there and develop our own production, regardless of the daily operations of the refinery.\n\nIn addition, Karatbars and more recently, has partnered with the best gold producer in Germany, \"Degussa\" and \"Nadir Metal\", which together with Atasay, are the best producers in Turkey.\n\nIn our featured products, we can recommend country cards, with our 1 gram gold. They are special cards, and with glorious colors showing the respective national flags. These Karatbars gold ingots are characterized by their distinction and finishing of the highest quality.\n\nYou also have the opportunity to purchase collectible and limited edition gold cards. Our goal is to offer different editions with a variety of interesting topics. Since we often need a license for these cards, the price differs a bit from the normal gold card.\n\nKaratbars International, only offers ingots of pure gold, of 999.9, of the highest quality in production and with the best certifications and supports.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_7">\nIs it really gold?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_8">Yes, the ingots of 1 gram, 2.5 grams and 5 grams are 24 carat gold with a purity of 999% of refineries certified by the London Bullion Market Association (LBMA).\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_9">\nWhy are ingots so small?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_10">Because the Karatbars mission is to offer people of all types and conditions the possibility of accessing savings with gold. People with little income can already save with gold, something that was not possible before. And people with high incomes have the ability to get their gold in a comfortable, discreet, and easy to store and transport.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_11">\nCan I get advice about my purchase decision?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_12">Our team is worldwide throughout the day. We also provide information and video presentations so you can learn in detail why you should invest in gold. The decision of when and how much to invest in gold, however, is up to you. To help you make a consensual decision and with what we offer, you can, for free, subscribe to our newsletter to get updates and news about current market events.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_13">\nAre the karatbars ingots expensive?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_14">Not at all, all gold distribution companies add a Premium to the market price that is their profit margin. The price of Karatbars ingots is precisely that of the daily market plus the Premium, which is why it changes. In addition, there is an annual discount bonus of 3%. There may be companies that put the price of the gram somewhat cheaper, although many others make it even more expensive. The advantage is that Karatbars distributes part of that Premium with its affiliates through commissions. And in that way, the real price of each gram of gold may end up being much lower than the market price itself, even if it covers it completely and goes free.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_15">\nHow can I buy karatbars ingots?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_16">Through the Karatbars website, registering as \"costumer\" or \"affiliate\".\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_17">\nWhat types of payments do you accept?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_18">It can be paid with debit, credit or prepaid card; with e-wallet; and in certain countries by bank transfer.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_19">\nDo they send me the gold home?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_20">Yes, Karatbars sends the bullion physically through the FEDEX messaging service.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_21">\nHow long will it take to receive the gold?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_22">The maximum period of reception is six weeks if paid by card, since it is manufactured on demand, however, at this time the average is about three weeks.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_23">\nCan you store my gold?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_24">Yes, you can also store gold for free in the vaults of Karatbars in Germany with maximum security, monitored by the company PROSEGUR.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_25">\nIs Karatbars International a bank?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_26">No. Karatbars International is a private and independent company, with physical headquarters, and with an Internet presence, for the purchase and sale of gold in small units. We work in more than 120 countries around the world, offering not only \"normal\" gold bullion cards, but also country cards and limited edition collection cards. Through direct contracts with producers, we work without intermediaries, which allows us to offer reasonable and competitive prices and fair conditions.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_27">\nWhy is Karatbars cheaper than a bank?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_28">Karatbars is an independent commercial company, with presence on the Internet and not a bank. As a direct supplier, we source the most competitive in the market and sell in our online store 24/7 for our global customers. The Internet allows us synergies and cost advantages that directly benefit you. This allows us to make our prices and conditions as competitive as possible for you.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_29">\nHow does Karatbars guarantee the security of my data during the transaction through the Internet?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_30">We guarantee the secure transmission of data by using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. With SSL, your information and personal data, which you enter in our encrypted website, are insured, so it can only be read by us.\n\nThe SSL encryption protocol has been established as the market standard for data through the Internet and is continuously being developed. Our privacy policy is total, see the section \"Privacy\" in the footer of our website.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_31">\nHow do I get to the customer area and what is offered to me?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_32">First, you must register for free. Next, you will receive your username and password. The closed area can be accessed through the \"Login\" button in the upper right corner of the page.\n\nCustomers and business partners can access, through the start of the session, their personal platform with all the agreed functions. Immediately after receipt of the completed registration forms, you can start immediately with Karatbars.\n\nIn the user area, you will find our offers and contents for specific customers and purchase.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_33">\nDoes Karatbars offer a repurchase service?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_34">Yes, Karatbars offers a repurchase service with one of the highest market prices.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_35">\nCan I buy in stores with my gold Karatbars?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_36">Yes, Karatbars has a network of associated businesses that accept Karatbar gold bullion as payment for their articles and services.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_37">\nCan I also recommend the Karatbars ingots and get commissions for it?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_38">Yes, by registering on the Karatbars website as an \"affiliate\" you obtain the license of an independent Karatbars distributor.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_39">\nCan I also register my business in the network of associated businesses?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_40">Yes, after registering your business on the Karatbars website as an \"affiliate\", you can also register it in the network of associated businesses through the K-Exchange program.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_41">\nDo I have to pay to join Karatbars as an affiliate?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_42">Registration as an affiliate in Karatbars is free and you can immediately start recommending and selling gold Karatbars.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_43">\nWhat commissions do I receive as an affiliate?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_44">Free registration as an affiliate entitles you to a commission by volume. In addition, there is the possibility of acquiring some \"franchise packages\" that open a range of other types of very important commissions.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_45">\nHow does Karatbars pay their commissions?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_46">Karatbars pays its members through a prepaid card issued by MasterCard, not linked to any bank account, and through a banking system called \"e-wallet\". Karatbars is concerned about the authentic financial independence of its members.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_47">\nMy first online sale, how does it work?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_48">Comfortable and without complications. If you have stored your gold with Karatbars:\n\nFirst, you give us an online sales order by email with your account number.\nSecond, your gold will be sold from your online account at the current re-purchase price.\nThird, you will receive your money within a few days in your account.\n\nIf you kept your gold personally:\n\nFirst, let us know by email, how much gold you give us, including your account number.\nSecond, you will receive a firm offer with the values ​​according to our Karatbars market price.\nThird, our logistics partner looks for the goods on your behalf.\nFourth, we examine the authenticity and recyclability of your assets. If everything goes well, as soon as possible, the agreed purchase price, minus the transfer costs are credited to the account specified by you, or:\nFifth, if your assets are returned to their original state, contrary to expectations, we contact you by telephone.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_49">\nI would like to change my password. How?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_50">To change your password, please enter with the previous access data in \"My Karatbars\", one go to \"Profile\" and then \"Edit password\". Now you can easily change your password.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_51">\nError Messages Who can help me?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_52">Do you have an error message on the screen? Do not worry, our PyR service (Questions and Answers) offers virtual assistance. Simply click on the upper right corner of \"PyR\" and click on the appropriate question.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_53">\nIs not the answer correct?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_54">Please, contact us by email at support@karatbars.com We will contact you as soon as possible within the next 24 hours.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_55">\nWhat are the delivery and reception costs?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_56">The shipping and delivery costs depend on both the value and the quantity of the goods, as well as the shipping method and the weight. The relevant delivery costs are shown in the payment process. Note: The card with the 1 gram ingot weighs about 8 g! This means that, if we send you 100 g of gold, this is a total weight of 800 g.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_57">\nMy goods have not arrived yet! Who can help me?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_58">If you have already received notification by email that your merchandise has been delivered to the logistics company and yet a day has passed and a request for a delivery date from the logistics company has not been received, then you must to know:\n\nIn exceptional cases (air strike or adverse weather conditions), there may be occasional delays. If this were the case, we will notify immediately so we can take care of the whereabouts of your delivery. We sit down with our logistics partner and always clarify the facts for you. Through FedEx, you will receive a transaction number. There you can see exactly where your package is at the moment.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_59">\nWhat happens if I\'m not at home at the time of delivery?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_60">You have to be at home at the time of delivery to sign the receipt your package. If you are not at home for the specified time, our logistics partner will leave the notification in the e-mail box. Keep in mind, in this case, that you will have to contact the logistics company for a new appointment. Any additional expense or re-shipping will have to be assumed by you. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause. Thank you.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_61">\nWhat to do if the delivery is incompatible with the content of the shipment?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_62">Karatbars has provided different security controls. In an optimized sequence of checks, the content of your shipment is electronically weighted under video surveillance and compared to the calculated target weight.\n\nIf despite all the controls at the time of shipment, there are discrepancies, please inform us immediately.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_63">\nWhat is \"My Karatbars\" and what are the benefits for me?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_64">My Karatbars \"is your own access to the virtual world of the Karatbars trade.\n\nIt offers simple and convenient functions for buying or selling gold bullion and commercialization products, and provides valuable and current information on the precious metals market. We provide an online gold trade.\n\nWith the \"My Karatbars\" function you will always have an overview of your current orders and sales. Under the button \"Gold Account\" and \"General Account View\" you will receive the history of your purchases. \"My Karatbars\" handles main data such as account information, shipping addresses and your correspondence with Karatbars. You will also find all forms and documents available for download. \"\n\n\"What you want to do: have the opportunity in\" your \"Karatbars to\" do it yourself \".\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_65">\nWhat happens to the information I have given to you?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_66">Certain information that we collect to process the transaction. We treat all information confidentially and with absolute care. A transfer of data or access by unauthorized persons is excluded. Your data is stored only in our company. All of our employees are subject to a confidentiality agreement and we are committed to using that information solely for the purpose of processing your transactions with Karatbars. \"\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_67">\nWho should I contact if I forget my password?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_68">You can instantly request your new password online. Go to the LOGIN page and click on the appropriate entry box under the \"Forgot Password?\" Button. You will immediately receive an email from our Support Team.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_69">\nWhat advantages do I have when I buy or sell precious metals in Karatbars?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_70">Whether you buy or sell, with Karatbars you get quality and price. Because we work directly with producers and refiners, without intermediaries! We have our own production line at the ATAKULCHE refinery in Turkey (Istanbul). That is why we can control the volume of production, to be able to supply our customers quickly.\n\nA production with delivery can take up to 6 weeks (depending on the country). We talk about maximum time always. For Spain, for example, gold shipments can take up to 2 weeks at present. The order of the goods to the producer will be made immediately after receiving the payment. Even if you have a special request, we will be happy to supply you.\n\nUnlike other gold trading houses, we get the gold directly from the producer. We translate this advantage into improving the prices for you and our business partners.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_71">\nHow can I place an order in Karatbars?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_72">Too easy. Enter now with your access data, in your personal administrative area. Click on Profile and on KYC, these are the documents to confirm your identification. You must send the requested documents. In 24 hours maximum, you will be activated.\n\nThen go to Buy Gold, select the desired category and enter the desired amount. In a few minutes you can request your Gold Card (s). If you pay by credit card, the number of your purchase bullion is shown in real time.\n\nIf you want to make a transfer, click on Bank Transfer. A PDF file will be generated with your username and your personal ID number (please always specify in the transfers). If you scroll down in the PDF file you will find the bank details. You must transfer the amount of the invoice.\n\nWe inform you about your payments to our account from your gold account in your personal area. The gold you buy is always confirmed. Your assets will always be accounted for by our staff, 2 people from Karatbars and a video surveillance camera.\n\nOur logistics partners will contact you to arrange a delivery schedule that is convenient for you. Through FedEx, you can even track delivery over the Internet.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_73">\nCan I sell my gold Karatbars?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_74">Of course you can also sell us your precious metals. Comfortable and without complications.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_75">\nDo you have to renew the license every year through a payment?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_76">Registration as an affiliate is free and you do not have to renew it every year. Franchise packages are purchased only once and do not have to be renewed each year.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_77">\nDo you have to buy stock every month to collect?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_78">The commission charge does not depend on any personal monthly purchase. Moreover, in the Karatbars business it is not necessary to keep any stock because customers buy directly through the web, and Karatbars takes care of the whole process.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_79">\nIs the Karatbars business system a pyramid scheme?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_80">Not at all, Karatbars is a legal e-commerce company that complies with all the legislation in force in each country in which it operates.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_81">\nWhy is KYC necessary?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_82">KYC stands for Know Your Customer. In order to be able to make purchases of Karatbar gold products, it will be necessary to verify your identity and residence. After approval, you can make your first purchase. Please make sure that your documents meet the following requirements:\n\n1. Valid government identification scanned in color. The name must be the same as in the Back Office. The photograph must be clearly visible, as well as the date of birth and validity.\n2. Receipt of services (gas, telephone, water, etc.) NO more than six months. The name of the company should be clear, as well as its name, address and date of issue. NO ENVELOPES, SCREEN CAPTURES OR ELECTRONIC DOCUMENTS ARE ACCEPTED.\n\nFor companies, additional documentation will be required:\n\n3. Incorporation documents, documents of the organization, etc. (complete documentation as it was entered into your State or Government). Companies registered in Karatbars must be in a \"Good Position\".\n4. Evidence that the person entering the documentation is authorized to contract and conduct business transactions on behalf of the Company.\n5. EIN / VAT, etc. document.\n\nTAKE INTO ACCOUNT: Karatbars verify the information with different regulators, but it may be the case of requiring additional documentation by the affiliates or depending on the situation. IMPORTANT: The identification document and the proof of address and / or the registration document of the company must be kept in different files. However, the company\'s registration document must be uploaded in a single PDF since it is considered a single information package. The above will speed up the approval process.\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_83">\nHOW DO I CONTACT KARATBARS?</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_84">Karatbars International GmbH\nVaihingerstrasse 149a\n70567 Stuttgart, Deutschland\nEUROPA Soporte: +49 711 128 970 00\nUS Soporte: + 1 224 829 00 47\n</string>
    <string name="large_text_faqs_contacto">Hispanic Manager, Elizabeth Cruz: elizabeth.cruz@karatbars.com\nEverything related to my prepaid Karatbars MasterCard: debitcard@karatbars.com\nRequests in Spanish: help@karatbars.com\nGeneral Requests: support@karatbars.com\nKYC approval: kyc@karatbars.com\nEverything related to my shipments: delivery@karatbars.com\nBranding Cards: brandingcards@karatbars.com\n</string>
    <string name="main_card3_button">Read...</string>
    <string name="main_card3_details">More details</string>
    <string name="main_card3_subtitle">Questions and Answers</string>
    <string name="main_card3_title">FAQs</string>
    <string name="main_card4_button_1">See more...</string>
    <string name="main_card4_button_2">More here</string>
    <string name="about_card2_title">If you liked the app, feel free to contact me.</string>
    <string name="about_card1_message">Karatbars Visionary Boys Club presents a way to financial freedom. Do you join our club?</string>
    <string name="about_not_found_email">Not found email app</string>
    <string name="about_google_play">Rate on Google play</string>
    <string name="about_email">Feedback by E-mail</string>
    <string name="about_address">Havana, Cuba</string>
    <string name="about_source_licenses">Open source licenses</string>
    <string name="about_website">View my website</string>
    <string name="about_version">Version:</string>
    <string name="activity_donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="main_card4_text_noticias">News</string>
    <string name="main_card4_text_apps">Apps</string>
    <string name="nav_donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="nav_crypto">Cryptocurrencies Karatbars</string>
    <string name="nav_about">About...</string>
    <string name="nav_faq">FAQs</string>
    <string name="nav_header_text">Karatbars Visionary Boys Club</string>
    <string name="nav_karatbars">Karatbars</string>
    <string name="nav_my_apps">Karatbars Apps</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Closed navigation drawer.</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer.</string>
    <string name="donate_title">"I Would Be Very Grateful If You Could Donate Me ! "</string>
    <string name="donate_title_after">"Thanks For Your Donations, I Am Very Grateful ! "</string>
    <string name="donated">Donated</string>
    <string name="donate_KCB">KCB</string>
    <string name="donate_KBC">KBC</string>
    <string name="donate_ETH">ETH</string>
    <string name="donate_BTC">BTC</string>
    <string name="donate_UNV">UNV</string>
    <string name="donate_exception">Sorry, can not do this!</string>
    <string name="item_swipe_dismissed">Dismissed</string>
    <string name="item_swipe_undo">Undo</string>
    <string name="no_more_data">No more data</string>
    <string name="share_view_press_it">You can press it</string>
    <string name="about_sigueme_en_fb">Follow me on Facebook</string>
    <string name="about_sigueme_en_instagram">Follow me on Instagram</string>
    <string name="about_sigueme_en_twitter">Follow me on twitter</string>
    <string name="large_text_bienvenidos_1">\n\nPresentation of Karatbars International GbmH</string>
    <string name="large_text_bienvenidos_2">Karatbars International emerged in 2011 to the idea of Mr. Harald Seiz who is CEO and founder of the company. \n\nThis company is currently active in more than 120 countries. Its headquarters are located in Stuttgart, Germany. Its goal is to produce nothing more and nothing less than gold bars 999.9 thousandths of purity of 24k in small quantities of 1 gram, 2.5 and 5 grams making this product affordable for any pocket.\n\nThis is the highest quality gold available and comes sealed in a high quality plastic the size of a credit card and is fully accredited by the LBMA, for its acronym, the Precious Metals Market Association of London.  \n\nNow let me make it clear, we are not asking anyone to buy something, we are simply exchanging a part of our paper money for real money, which is gold. \n \nSo let me ask you a question here: If you could exchange a part of your paper currency for physical gold 999.9 thousandths of purity of 24k produced by the refinery accredited by the LBMA and earn a juicy commission for only referring others, it would ? \n \nMost likely yes. I think that only a few times in life there is a really fantastic opportunity on our way, and that some people let go, and then they complain saying, oh, but he got lucky, she got lucky, or they have good contacts, education adequate, the circle of appropriate friendships and blah blah blah blah ... and never assume their responsibility and take advantage of these opportunities.  \n\nWell, I think luck is defined as when the opportunity coincides with the preparation, and I think this is one of those occasions when the opportunity knocks on your door. But the question is: Are you prepared to take advantage of it? \n\nI hope so for your good.\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="qc_code_close">Close</string>
    <string name="qr_code_auto_scan_notification">Position QR Code</string>
    <string name="qr_code_camera_not_found">Could not detect camera</string>
    <string name="qr_code_camera_not_open">Could not open your camera</string>
    <string name="qr_code_close_flash_light">Close Flash Light</string>
    <string name="qr_code_could_not_read_qr_code_from_picture">Could not read your image.Try another image~</string>
    <string name="qr_code_could_not_read_qr_code_from_scanner">Sorry, could not open scan content</string>
    <string name="qr_code_notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="qr_code_open_flash_light">Open flash light</string>
    <string name="qr_code_positive_button_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="qr_code_positive_button_know">OK</string>
    <string name="qr_code_select_picture">Picture</string>
    <string name="shortcut_label_about">About</string>
    <string name="permiso_cancelar">Cancel</string>
    <string name="permiso_configuracion">SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="permiso_error">Error Occurred!</string>
    <string name="permiso_necesario_subtitle">This app needs permission to use this feature. You can grant them in app settings.</string>
    <string name="permiso_necesario_title">Need Permissions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scan_qr_code">Scan</string>
    <string name="tv_recycler_item_1">Swipe down to refresh</string>
    <string name="tv_recycler_item_2">Swipe left or right to dismiss it</string>
    <string name="tv_recycler_item_3">Drag up or down to move it</string>
    <string name="title_activity_share_view">Share View</string>
    <string name="shortcut_label_scrolling">Scrolling</string>
    <string name="shortcut_label_recycler">Recycler View</string>
    <string name="about_ver_codigo_github">Source Code on GitHub</string>
    <string name="name">QRCodeScanner</string>
    <string name="nav_calificar">Rate</string>
    <string name="internet_problem">Something went wrong. Check your Internet connection.</string>
</resources>